pricedoc.com 2011-11-28

# Privacy Policy | PriceDoc - Better Price + Better Healthcare.

### PriceDoc, Inc. Website Privacy Statement

This document was last updated on 1/27/2009.

PriceDoc Inc. is a Participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. As this Web site (www.pricedoc.com) wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at info@pricedoc.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

PriceDoc, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing pricedoc.com, you acknowledge and fully understand PriceDoc, Inc’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

If changes to our privacy policy are made, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES**

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in PriceDoc, Inc. services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

PriceDoc, Inc. collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

**Web Server Logs**

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: 

      * Your Internet protocol address. 
      * The kind of browser or computer you use. 
      * Number of links you click within the site. 
      * State or country from which you accessed the site. 
      * Date and time of your visit. 
      * Name of your Internet service provider. 
      * Web page you linked to our site from. 
      * Pages you viewed on the site. 

**Use of Cookies**

PriceDoc, Inc. may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. If used these cookies do not contain in PII (Personal Identity Information)

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

PriceDoc, Inc. does use third-party analytic reporting that do utilize cookies. No PII (Personal Identity Information) is shared with any third party.

**Personal Information Users**

Visitors to our web site can register to purchase services. When our users register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number, account number and other relevant information. PriceDoc, Inc collects information from visitors, users, and consumers who access various parts of our web site. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide our users with a highly customized online experience. Among other things, we use visitor contact information to send provider coupons, contact prior visitors to inform, survey, or review their coupon redemption status or appointment with a provider, and to send service and promotional emails. Promotional emails will be sent from PriceDoc, Inc.

If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

      * To fulfill your service requests for services. 
      * To protect ourselves from liability, 
      * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
      * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES**

pricedoc.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow PriceDoc, Inc. to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. PriceDoc, Inc. may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. PriceDoc, Inc. prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

**SECURITY**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. 

An SSL Encryption is utilized on all pages where sensitive financial information is collected.

**ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant – info@pricedoc.com.

**CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**

PriceDoc, Inc. reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**CONTACTING US**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at info@pricedoc.com or send your comments to:

PriceDoc, Inc.  
**Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel**  
PriceDoc, Inc.  
249 S. Highway 101, Suite 577  
Solana Beach, CA 

PriceDoc, Inc. will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
